RG 002:025, Select Committee of Inquiry to Recommend Whether Sufficient Grounds Exist for the House of Representatives to Impeach Governor John G. Rowland Pursuant to Article Ninth of the State Constitution
Connecticut State Library
Select Committee of Inquiry records
1978-2004
bulk 1995-2004
2004
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. General Assembly. Select Committee of Inquiry
210 cubic feet
On January 26, 2004, House Resolution 702 formally established the Select Committee of Inquiry to determine whether sufficient grounds existed to impeach Governor John G. Rowland. Speaker of the House Moira K. Lyons (D-Stamford) appointed Arthur J. O'Neill (R-Southbury) and John Wayne Fox (D-Stamford) as co-chairmen.
RG002_025_SCOI
Historical Note
A press report on November 25, 2003 raised questions about who paid for renovations to Governor John G. Rowland's cottage on Bantam Lake in Litchfield, Connecticut. Governor Rowland denied that free work had been done at the cottage. On December 12, 2003, Governor Rowland issued a statement admitting that he had provided inaccurate and incomplete information about the cottage work. He apologized to the press and the citizens of Connecticut and disclosed that friends, members of his staff, state employees and state contractors had paid for or provided free work. He denied that any of these individuals or entities received any benefit from his office or the state in exchange for their involvement at the cottage. A wide range of other issues came under media scrutiny, including the lease and sale of a Washington, D. C. condominium and gifts and vacations he had received or taken.
On January 14, 2004, Speaker of the House Moira K. Lyons (D-Stamford) announced that the House of Representatives would form a bipartisan committee to consider whether to recommend Governor Rowland's impeachment. On January 26, 2004, House Resolution 702 formally established the Select Committee of Inquiry. Lyons appointed Arthur J. O'Neill (R-Southbury) and John Wayne Fox (D-Stamford) as co-chairmen. The Resolution did not limit the scope of the Committee's inquiry, but did set an initial deadline for the work of April 14, 2004. This deadline was extended to May 5, 2004, and later to June 30, 2004.
On February 11, 2004, the Select Committee retained Steven F. Reich of the law firm Manatt, Phelps & Phillips, LLP to serve as Special Counsel. The Committee then adopted rules and procedures, defined the scope and priorities of investigation, and identified and considered appropriate standards for impeachment. On February 19, 2004, the Committee adopted procedures governing the receipt and presentation of evidence. It issued its first document subpoenas on February 26, 2004. In all, the Committee issued a total of 140 document subpoenas, conducted hundreds of witness interviews and gathered approximately 409,000 pages of documents. On March 19, 2004, the Committee adopted rules governing depositions. It deposed five individuals: Mary Ann Hanley, Michael Cicchetti, Marc Ryan, David O'Leary and Jo McKenzie.
On February 26, 2004, the Committee served document subpoenas on the Governor and Mrs. Rowland but the documents were not submitted. On April 30, 2004, it issued further subpoenas to the Governor and Mrs. Rowland to appear before the Committee to testify regarding their failure to comply with the document subpoenas. Neither appeared nor designated a representative to testify on their behalf. The Committee ordered its Special Counsel to draft an article of impeachment against the Governor based on his failure to cooperate with the inquiry. The article of impeachment was presented to the Committee on May 14, 2004 but while the Committee accepted the draft article, it deferred its consideration until the conclusion of the inquiry.
The Committee faced a number of obstacles. The ongoing federal grand jury investigation into alleged misconduct in the Rowland Administration limited the Committee's ability to gather information. Many of the witnesses whose testimony and documents were relevant to the inquiry were also integral to the federal investigation. A number of key witnesses invoked their constitutional right against self-incrimination and declined to respond to the Committee's demands for information. The Committee also faced resistance in the form of litigation challenging its subpoena authority, including litigation filed by the Governor's Office. On May 18, 2004, the Select Committee served a subpoena on the Governor requiring his testimony as the first witness at public evidentiary hearings. On June 1, 2004, the Office of the Governor filed a complaint in Hartford Superior Court for injunctive and declaratory relief against the Committee, seeking a ruling that the subpoena violated the constitution separation of powers.
The Superior Court denied the relief sought by the Governor's Office. The Governor's Office then sought certification of the matter directly to the Connecticut Supreme Court. On June 18, 2004, the Supreme Court denied the Governor's motion to quash the Committee's Subpoena. As a result, on June 21, 2004, Governor Rowland announced his resignation from office, effective July 1, 2004. Due to the resignation, the Committee suspended its evidentiary hearings and its final report made no recommendation on whether Governor Rowland's conduct warranted impeachment.
Source.
Scope and Content
Series 1, Administrative Files, documents the work of the Committee. It is further arranged into subseries. Standards and Procedures includes submissions from Steven F. Reich, counsel to the Select Committee of Inquiry, Ross H. Garber, counsel to the Office of the Governor, and William F. Dow, personal counsel to Governor John G. Rowland. Reports includes copies of the draft and final report of the Committee. Committee Meetings includes agendas, minutes and transcripts. Basic Legal Documents include various motions filed on behalf of the Committee, the Office of the Governor, and other individuals and entities including: Tomasso Brothers, Inc.; TBI Construction Company, LLC; Tunxis Management Company; Tenergy Water, LLC; Michael Tomasso; William Tomasso; Peter Ellef; Cocchiola Paving and Anthony Cocchiola. Correspondence includes incoming and outgoing correspondence primarily of the Committee co-chairmen John Wayne Fox and Arhthur J. O'Neill and counsel Steven F. Reich. Included are copies of e-mails. Civil Summonses are lawsuits against the Committee by various plaintiffs including: Peter Ellef; Robert V. Matthews; TBI Construction Company, LLC; Tunxis Management Company; Tenergy Water, LLC; Michael Tomasso; William Tomasso; Cocchiola Paving, Inc.; Anthony Cocchiola; Mark Wertheim; Patrick J. Delahunty; Vincent J. DeRosa; Tunxis Plantation Country Club; and Michael H. Cicchetti. There is also one summons for suit of the Committee against the Freedom of Information Commission. Subpoenas include copies of subpoenas served to over one hundred individuals and entities. Hearing Exhibits are duplicates of Series 3. Depositions include transcripts of the five individuals deposed: Michael H. Cicchetti; Mary Ann Hanley; Jo McKenzie; David O'Leary; and Marc S. Ryan. Freedom of Information Act includes requests, hearing notices, decisions and appeals.
Also included in the Administrative Files are Committee membership lists, media advisories, news articles, personnel and business records.
Series 2, Subpoenaed Documents contain unredacted documents submitted to the Committee from various individuals, state agencies, organizations, and businesses.
Series 3, Evidentiary Hearing Exhibits were taken from subpoenaed documents. There are two duplicate sets of exhibits.
Series 4, Evidentiary Hearing Videotapes are present for all but the second hearing day. The number of copies for each hearing day range from two to nine. There is also a video disc of a news briefing following the State Ethics Commission Meeting on September 29, 2004.
Arrangement
Arranged in four series:
Series 1, Administrative Files, 1978-2004, is further arranged into the following subseries: Procedures and Standards; Membership; Reports; Committee Meetings; Basic Legal Documents; Correspondence; Media Advisories; Civil Summonses; Subpoenas; Hearing Exhibits; Depositions; Freedom of Information Act; News Articles; Personnel; and Business Records. The standards and procedures, reports, committee meetings, basic legal documents, correspondence, media advisories, civil summonses, and news articles are arranged chronologically. Hearing exhibits are arranged numerically by assigned exhibit number. Subpoenas and depositions are arranged alphabetically.
Series 2, Subpoenaed Documents, circa 1995-2004, are arranged by Bates number. Each individual and entity subpoenaed was assigned an alphabetic code. Each piece of paper received was stamped with a Bates number comprised of the code for the party that submitted it concatenated with a number. The first sheet of paper submitted was 00001 and the number for each subsequent sheet was incremented by one. For example, there are five pieces of paper submitted by Anthony Autorino. The first piece of paper was stamped AA00001, the second was stamped AA00002, etc. The Department of Transportation submitted a large amount of documents too late for them to be assigned Bates numbers. These documents are unprocessed at the end of the series.
Series 3, Evidentiary Hearing Exhibits, circa 1989-2004 are arranged numerically by the assigned exhibit number.
Series 4, Evidentiary Hearing Videotapes, 2004 are arranged chronologically.
Related Material
None.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. General Assembly. Select Committee of Inquiry
Persons:
Rowland, John G., 1957-
Subjects:
Connecticut. General Assembly. Select Committee of Inquiry -- Records and correspondence; Rowland, John G., 1957- -- Impeachment; Impeachments -- Connecticut; Misconduct in office -- Connecticut; Governors -- Connecticut -- Discipline; Connecticut -- Politics and government -- 1951-
Document Types:
Correspondence; Depositions; Legal documents; Membership lists; Minutes; Reports; Subpoenas; Summonses
Restrictions on Access
Series 1, Administrative Files, subseries Subpoenas is restricted. Some subpoenas include the social security number of the person serving the subpoena. Subpoenas to financial institutions may contain account information. Please contact State Archives staff for assistance.
Series 2, Subpoenaed Documents (entire) is restricted because it contains personal information such as social security numbers and financial account numbers. Please see the Alternate Form Available section below.
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Alternative Form Available
Redacted versions of Series 2, Subpoenaed Documents are available on a hard drive through the Law and Legislative Reference unit. [CSL call number StLib Law Vault Conn Doc G253r]
Provenance
The evidentiary hearing exhibits and videotapes were deposited at the State Library in 2004. The administrative files and subpoenaed documents were deposited in 2006.
Container List
- Series 1. Administrative Files, 1978-2004; bulk 2004
  - Standards and Procedures
    - Committee procedures, 2004 January-February (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bill 5665, 2004 February (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Steven Reich's report on standards, 2004 March 5 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Ross Garber's submission on standards, 2004 March (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - William F. Dow's letter on standards, 2004 March 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Steven Reich's submission on standards, 2004 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Ross Garber's presentation on standards, 2004 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - William F. Dow's letter on rules and procedures, 2004 March 26 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Ross Garber's letter on deposition procedure, 2004 April 12 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Extensions of time, 2004 April-May (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Deposition procedures, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Reference resources, 2004 February, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Membership (Box 1)
    - Membership list, 2004 February (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Reports (Box 1)
    - Certification of report on subpoenas, 2004 April 12 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Drafts, 2004 May-June (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Final report, 2004 June (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Committee Meetings (Box 1)
    - Agendas and minutes (Box 1)
      - 2004 January-February (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - 2004 March (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - 2004 April (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - 2004 May-June (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Transcripts (Box 1)
      - Steven F. Reich opening statement, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
      - 2004 January 30-February 4 (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - 2004 February 11-13 (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - 2004 February 19-26 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - 2004 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - 2004 March 19 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - 2004 April 19 (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - 2004 April 30-May 14 (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - 2004 May 24 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Basic Legal Documents (Box 1)
    - Appearances, 2004 March-April (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Steven F. Reich Ex Parte application for Pro Hac Vice, 2004 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Memorandum of decision, Tomasso Brothers, Inc. v. Richard A. Blumenthal as Attorney General, 2004 March 5 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Select Committee motion to consolidate actions, 2004 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - TBI Construction Company, LLC; Tunxis Management Company; Tenergy Water, LLC; Michael Tomasso; and William Tomasso amended complaint for injunctive and declaratory relief, 2004 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Peter Ellef amended complaint for injunctive and declaratory relief, 2004 March 15 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Select Committee motion to dismiss, 2004 March 16 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Cocchiola Paving and Anthony Cocchiola objection to motion to dismiss, 2004 March 22 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Peter Ellef objection to motion to dismiss, 2004 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - TBI Construction, Tunxis Management, Tenergy Water, Michael and William Tomasso opposition to motion to dismiss, 2004 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Withdrawals, 2004 March 23 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Opposition to motion to stay order pending appeal in regards to Ex Parte application for Pro Hac Vice of Steven F. Reich, 2004 April 6 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Memorandum of decision on Select Committee motion to dismiss, 2004 April 8 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Select Committee motion for designation of related case for assignment purposes, 2004 April 16 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Select Committee motion for an emergency hearing for purposes of setting an expedited schedule for briefing and oral argument, 2004 April 16 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Select Committee notice of dismissal as to Michael H. Cicchetti and Cocchiola Pavings, Inc., 2004 April 22 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Select Committee application for an order enforcing subpoenas, 2004 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Gov. Rowland motion to withdraw or, alternatively, to quash subpoena, 2004 April 30 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Office of the Governor complaint for injunctive and declaratory relief, 2004 May 27 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Memorandum of law in support of Office of the Governor motion to quash, 2004 May 27 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Select Committee motion for permission to exceed page limitation on memorandum of law, 2004 June 2 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Select Committee memorandum of law in opposition to Office of Governor motion to quash and for preliminary and permanent injunctive relief, 2004 June 2 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Office of Governor appeal from Superior Court, 2004 June (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence (Box 1)
    - 2004 January-March, 4 folders (Box 1, Folder 53-56)
    - 2004 April-May, 3 folders (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
    - E-mails (Box 2)
      - 2004 January-May, 40 folders (Box 2, Folder 4-43)
      - 2004 June-2005, 28 folders (Box 3, Folder 1-28)
  - Media Advisories, 2004 March-April (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Civil Summonses (Box 3)
    - Ellef, Peter, 2004 March 4 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Matthews, Robert V., 2004 March 4 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - TBI Construction Company, LLC, 2004 March 4 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - TBI Construction Company, LLC; Tunxis Management Company, 2004 March 4 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - TBI Construction Company, LLC; Tunxis Management Company; Tenergy Water, LLC; Michael Tomasso; and William Tomasso, 2004 March 30 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Cocchiola Paving, Inc.; Anthony Cocchiola, 2004 March 8 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Wertheim, Mark, 2004 March 8 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Delahunty, Patrick J., 2004 March 11 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - DeRosa, Vincent J., 2004 March 11 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Tunxis Plantation Country Club, Inc., 2004 April 6 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Cicchetti, Michael H., 2004 April 14 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Select Committee of Inquiry, 2004 May 7 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Subpoenas
    RESTRICTED. Please contact State Archives staff for assistance.
    - List of subpoenas, 2004 February 26-May 3 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Service lists, 2004 April-May (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Tracking, 2004 February-May (Box 4, Folder 3-6)
    - Contact information, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Application for enforcement of subpoenas, 2004 April 20-21 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Adams, Patrice, 2004 June 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Administrative Services, Dept. of, 2004 March-April (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Alibozek, Lawrence E., 2004 March, June (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - American Express Company, 2004 April 21-22 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - AMR Associates, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Anson, Theodore, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Astro Electric, Inc., 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Autorino, Anthony D., 2004 February 26-27 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Baker, Patrick and Sons, Inc., 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Bank One Credit Card Services, 2004 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Bilodeau, Robert, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Bond Commission, State, 2004 March 15-16 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Boos, Charles, 2004 June 1 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Calabrese & Kuncas, P.C., 2004 March 2 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Capital City Economic Development Authority, 2004 April 5 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Carmody & Torrance, LLP, 2004 April-May (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Cellco Partnership d/b/a Verizon Wireless, 2004 May 14-17 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Chalfield, Robert, 2004 April 8-9 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Children and Families, 2004 March 15-16 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Cicchetti & Tansley, LLP, 2004 February-April (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Citigroup, Inc., 2004 April 21-22 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - CMD Ventures, LLC, 2004 March 15-16 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Cocchiola, Anthony, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Cohn, Benson, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Columbia Funds Distributor, Inc., 2004 April 21-29 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Commercial Moving Services, LLC, 2004 March 15-16 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Competition Watersports, Inc., 2004 March 31 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Connecticut Development Authority, 2004 March-April (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Connecticut Housing Finance Authority, 2004 April 2-5 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Connecticut Innovations, Inc., 2004 April 2-5 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Connecticut Lottery Corporation, 2004 March-April (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Connecticut Natural Gas, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Corey, Christine, 2004 February-June (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Corey, Paul J., 2004 February 26-29 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Country Club of Waterbury, Inc., 2004 March-April (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Deal, Kelly, 2004 March 2 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Delahunty, P.J., 2004 March-June (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - DeRosa, Vincent J., 2004 March-June (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Devany, Corrine, 2004 June 1 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Dolphin Pools and Spas, 2004 March 15-16 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Economic and Community Development, Dept. of, 2004 March 2-3 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Ellef, Peter, 2004 February-June (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Environmental Protection, Dept. of, 2004 April 2-5 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Ethics Commission, State, 2004 February 26-27 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Executive Chambers Conservancy, Inc., 2004 March 31 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Executive Residence Conservancy, Inc., 2004-February-March (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Fabiani, Maurice, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Fabricated Metals Products, Inc., 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Fallon Moving & Storage, Inc., 2004 March 15-16 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - First Development Group, LLC, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - First Union National Bank, 2004 April 14-15 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - FleetBoston Financial Corporation, 2004 April-May (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Governor, Office of the, 2004 February-April (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Governor's Residence Conservancy, Inc., 2004 March 2-16 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Gray, Richard, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Hanley, Mary Ann, 2004 February-April (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Hartford Downtown Revival, LLC, 2004 March 15-16 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Heckman, James, 2004 June 1 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - HRW Associates, Inc. dba Sanditz Travel, 2004 May 5-7 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Information Technology, Dept. of, 2004 May 6 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - JP Morgan Chase & Co., 2004 April-May (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Key Air, Inc., 2004 May 11-14 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Lauzier, Glenn, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Lepak, Kathleen, 2004 June 1 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Link Mechanical Services, Inc., 2004 February-June (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Litchfield County Marine and Auto, LLC, 2004 March 24 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Mancini, Michael, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Maria's Travel Service, Inc. d/b/a Colonial Travel, 2004 May 11 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Matthews, Robert V., 2004 March-June (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Matthews Ventures, LLC, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - MBNA Corporation, 2004 April 21 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - McKenzie, Jo, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Mengacci, Kathleen, 2004 June 1 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Mikenas, Ed, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 2004 March 19 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - New Haven Manufacturing, 2004 March 1-3 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Nextel Communications of the Mid-Atlantic, Inc., 2004 March 31 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - O & G Industries, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - O'Leary, David, 2004 May 4 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Policy and Management, Office of, 2004 March-April (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Pratt, Wayne, 2004 March-June (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - PriceWaterhouse Coopers, LLP, 2004 April 27-28 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Properties Review Board, State, 2004 March 15-16 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Public Safety, Dept. of, 2004 April 2-5 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Public Works, Dept. of, 2004 February-March (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Quick & Reilly, Inc., 2004 May 4-5 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Ragaglia, Kristine, 2004 June 1 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - RMK Prospect Associates, LLC, 2004 February-March (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Rowland, John G., 2004 February-May (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Rowland, Patricia, 2004 February-May (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Rubin, Rachel, 2004 June 1 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Ryan, Marc S., 2004 April 22-23 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Santogatta, Michael, 2004 June 1 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Secor, Cassidy & McPartland, P.C., 2004 April 21 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Shared Technologies Cellular, Inc., 2004 February-March (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Shortell, Ron, 2004 February -June (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Special Revenue, Division of, 2004 April 2-5 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Stackpole, Moore & Tryon Company, 2004 April 8-9 (Box 5, Folder 13)